it's week 12 of me turning this into a
million day trading and I have a feeling
I'm going to have to use this this
week good morning ladies and gentlemen
before I get started today and I do a
trade update I want to take this second
to
appreciate the Iguana being here like I
don't I don't think you guys understand
what this means for this week last week
we ended off the week with the Iguana
there's a lot of people watching me give
me the
signal and now we started off the week
with the Iguana every single time the
Iguana comes we make money am I right Am
I Wrong do we not exactly what we're
about to do right now technically the
trades are loading so trade update right
now the account is exactly the same
currently at $200,000 on the account
obviously same exact history so GBP nzd
at the start of the yesterday we were
interested in Waiting for a quick retest
of this area to that sell and this would
have been our first take profit
2169 but price decided to just start off
the week and just have that push right
from the get we didn't not have the
retest and then sell even though yes we
did hit our takeprofit Zone we can still
technically enter this trade if it does
manage to pull back all the way up to
here because then it could create
another lower low leg so I don't love
this price action right now just sucks
that the actual move happened at the
start of the week without giving us the
retest that we wanted to but we're still
very much interested next is USD JPY
looks like it's currently building and
heading on its way up to here so we're
just going to remain very patient
waiting for price to retest this level
support support and round psychological
to then sell and then lastly Euro JPY we
are at that area right now where we're
looking to sell we are retesting the EMA
whoa retesting the EMA retesting
structure and retesting
160. now I'm going to be looking for my
entry signal here right around the maybe
1 hour time frame or 30 minute time
frame the only thing that I have to be
on the lookout for this is that if USD
JPY still has a lot more upside
potential to potentially make it year to
then sell that means that Euro JPY is
going to have that same push to the
upside so that means that this has a
prob probility of breaking through here
to then having the push once USD JPY
actually reaches this level so you got
to take that into consideration like
just because this trade is at the area
of Interest doesn't mean that it needs
to have the push right away and just
because this trade is not at the area of
interest does it mean that it's not
going to have the push right away this
one just definitely has more probability
of retesting this area rather than not
every single time we get close to it we
retest it when we're above when we're
under we retested multiple times when
we're under retested multiple times when
we're above we retested multiple times
so now that we're under I do expect for
it to retest so then that means that
this is just a fake out or an invalid
area of interest and then it's going to
make it up to then this next one that we
potentially don't even have marked up
here so very much on my toes with this
trade and looking at it very very
closely every hour and GBP nzd we're
just waiting for price to make it up
here to them so boring trade update it
is currently 8846 in the morning and
we'll update you guys as it goes if the
Iguana stays there oh
dude that's a sign bro that's a sign man
that is the sign best sign I can
possibly ask for this week to trade best
sign all right ladies and gentlemen good
evening so today it's been literally a
boring day been home all day haven't
done anything I haven't even left the
day haven't even left the day haven't
left my house today so it is currently
12:16 right now
the balance on the account is currently
exactly the same we still have not taken
another position in the account we're
still at
one come on
focus focus there you go
21,000 but tonight ladies and gentlemen
we're going to battle with the London
session guys we are literally going to
take the 200 to half million I don't
know if to tonight I would really want
it to be tonight but there's a high
possibility it is tonight the trades had
the move but are retracing to the air
Adventures that I anticipated on Sunday
with my students and I showed you guys
yesterday so let me show you guys right
now so first trade update is GBP nzd
where we are currently having a retest
of this structure level exactly how
we've been anticipating and when you go
down to the 4 Hour the 4 Hour is indeed
coming back exactly to this area how I
want wanted to what I love is that it
created the lower high and lower low and
it's having this pullback without
breaking the structure so this is still
technically the lower high this is still
technically the lower low whatever
happens in between here is nothing so
this structure pullback does not shift
the structure of the 4our so we can
enter this trade here rejecting the area
of interest and the EMA and it would be
a perfect entry because our structure is
still bearish I don't love that the 1
hour structure did go bullish because we
were lower low lower high lower low
lower high higher high now we're bullish
we're getting very clear rejection price
action on the 1 hour but I'm going to be
waiting for a little bit more of a shift
to structure on the 15 minute 30 minute
it's going to be a little bit more
selective on this trade simply because I
like a lot more USD JPY you guys can see
up here the time and the pairs so USD
JPY simply looks a lot cleaner earlier
today we were down here I was
anticipating for price to make it back
up here so technically I can remove this
and now I expecting price from this
point right here to have the P the
downside perfect left head potential
right shoulder daily time frame has come
back to retest that daily area of
Interest the previous daily body
Candlestick did close under
144,000 so now it looks like we're just
waking above kind of basically doing
what we did here last time I do love how
this is a very well respected level of
support and support
and I could very clearly see this having
a reaction tonight for London session
especially in London session I just need
a little bit more price action as soon
as we have a shift of structure on this
Market I'm going to be interested in
taking this trade this is the 30 minute
time frame right now you guys can see up
here to the top left corner so the only
way I would be interested in executing
this position is going to be at the
break and retest of this 30 minute
structure and that shi the structure on
the 30 minute is going to be absolutely
beautiful because and it's going to
create another potential Head and
Shoulders at the area of interest and
then breaking and
retesting
144,000 so it's going to be absolutely
perfect I'm going to put my alarm under
this 30 minute structure level and this
is going to confirm to me that we're
Shifting the structure so I'm going to
actually double click it and type in
here s oos shift of structure and then
last but not least Euro JPY which we
have clearly avoided a loss simply
because of the explanation that I gave
earlier Euro JPY yes it could be at the
area of interest and we could be ready
to sell but if USD JPY still has that
much room to make a backup into this
area it is just logically and
technically going to make sense that if
this has to have a deeper pullback to
them cell that this Market has to have a
deeper pullback as well it just happens
to be at a different area of interest
and we simply avoid this loss by
experience a lot of the Traders would
have seen this and entered the trade but
they would have not realized that they
could have cross correlated the pair
with this one because obviously they
both have JPY pairs so this is my number
one pair right now I'm very interested
in taking this trade as of right now
well not right now as soon as we get
structure but as of right now this is my
number one pair and the next would be
GBP nzd so stay tuned and I will update
you guys at this current Curr
12:21 in the morning oh and real quick
before we execute this trade and you
guys are about to go crazy with the
profits cuz I already I could already
see myself making this money don't go
crazy don't be like holy [__] that was
such a big trade I have to study exactly
what he did there so I can do it again
to make that much amount of money no at
all I'm only making
1.5% of the account obviously it's 150%
but we've done crazier flips in this
series go look at the week one where we
took 100 bucks to 3,000 reached the goal
for the week actively right now we are
currently up
$330 you guys can see here we made
3,000% to me 3,000% is far more
impressive than
150% now I get it it doesn't look
impressive because it's just 100 bucks
to 3K it doesn't sound like a big deal
but percentage wise it is a lot more
difficult and I have a lot more at risk
when I took the 100 to 3,000 taking
200 to 500 percentage wise it's a walk
in the park it is cake so I want to put
this into your guys' mindset so you guys
can really deeply understand that this
is a percentage game it is not a dollar
game it's not about the money it's about
the percentage the percentage is going
to directly influence the dollar amount
that you're supposed to make on the
trade so this is something that a lot of
Traders as soon as they get it they
start looking at the markets completely
different and I highly suggest it
quicker you implement it it's just going
to turn into a different game for you
it's it's can actually turn into a game
it's not going to so much turn into a
money thing it's just a game you just
want to get more percentage and the
percentage happens to equal money sounds
fun to me good morning ladies and
gentlemen I am not that energetic this
morning even though what we said last
night is happening slept for nothing I I
I I
missed just come here here trade update
I feel like I I feel like I've said this
a m million times trade update right now
we are up
$59,000 on the account but not only have
I said this a million times I'm talking
about this oh oh oh oh oh yo what is
going on every single time yo what the
[__] yo it's every time dude yo I can't
make this up dude yo I can't make this
[__] up bro I can't make this
up bro I was literally going to say we
have the head and shoulders pattern we
see this pattern a gazillion times and
then we usually always have the retest
to then sell dude what is happening dude
what is happening
bro all right well look at that there
goes our trade update right there we of
100,000 they'll go for the week as have
a ticket bro what's there come on do
your thing and dude I was just so calm I
was so relaxed I was so
Pacific well the goal was to show you
guys that what I said we needed
yesterday to happen which was The Head
and Shoulders we put our alarm at the
shift of structure and once we body
close under it we get the retest and
then we sell that's basically it we've
we've said it a 100 [__] times GBP
nzd we had a little bit of a nice push
last night we had the push to the
downside I just didn't like this pair
anywhere near as much as USD JPY because
we weren't at the hardcore area of
Interest how we are here gpusd still had
room to make it all the way up to here
so I didn't want to take that trade with
that much space and then Euro JPY I just
like USC JPY way better but pretty much
exactly what I anticipated is happening
right now bro what are we up there you
go you can't make this up dude you
cannot make this up okay so right now we
are up exactly
A1 to one and we're up about a
100,000 that means when we get to a 1 to
two we should be up 200,000 and when we
get to a 1 to three we'll be up 300,000
isn't that beautiful don't you want to
have your easy math like that every
single time you add a risk reward it's
just an extra 100K 100K 100K sounds good
to me so for now we're going to
definitely set and forget this John all
right trade up there boys let's see is
anything C crazy else going to happen
right now right now we are up about
118,000 the 30 minute time frame close
exactly how I wanted to retest very
bearish Candlestick to the downside 15
minute time frame we have beautiful 15
bearish and go from Candlestick looks
like it's retouching the structure we're
just destined to continue heading to the
downside so for now so don't forget I
can very easily Target very low in this
market but I'm just going to be watching
it one candle at a time I'm going to be
very patient I'm not going I'm very
excited internally but I'm not showing
it because the last time I did that we
blew the account can't let that happen
again I'm remaining very calm very
controlled and we'll update you guys in
the next hour or two trade update we're
up 20,000 Now isn't that crazy swings
from like a swings from being up 50k to
then Break Even In A Flash second then
up 100K then a little bit lower 150 and
now back up to
20,000 a regular human being a regular 9
to5 NPC
nin to fivr cannot handle this you're
not built for this respectfully right
right off the bat you could develop and
grow into it but that's what happens a
lot of ninet to FS they want to get into
trading and thinking that they're ready
for this you know this is something that
gets built over time you start cracking
uh your EG sh breaking out of the 9th
to5 mindset and your ability to be able
to manage and control
money so this is having a pullback looks
like it's retesting the neckline once
again so we were just up 20 now we're up
40 5 Seconds of talking [__] now we're
back at
30 oh man so for now set a fre up today
is a sad day um actually might cry
actually might cry so today's the day
that we have to get rid of the
Porsche bro touch my heart touch my
heart like for real for real for real
you going through bro literally so
before I get rid of it I just want to
say some things
because my Porsche so I'm just going to
read my letter to the Porsche to my
Porsche on who I've spent nine faithful
long months with you've been my first
Porsche and I have blown many tires with
you I'll miss you so much and our late
night Shenanigans and pushing your
buttons and flooring you to the rev
limiter I it's the days when I would
race you against other cars and you
would always lose because you're so slow
but you're trying your hardest and I
know it I'll make the smooth and perfect
transitions with the Rev matches every
single
time [__]
hurts I'll miss the way that you would
open the door handles when I unlock the
car just gives you the Sensation that
you want me to drive you but the most
important of all is I'll miss the
thousands of miles I shared with you
while you kept me safe and warm every
single time no matter the circumstance
or the tire condition you were always
ready for the adventure
my
Porche now you guys may be asking Alex
why are you setting the porsch what are
you going through why are you doing
that I
got why is he leaving so slow so you
have a chance to go get it
back let's go all right ladies and
gentlemen trade update it is currently
8:00 in the evening so not only is it a
sad day because my Porsche has left but
because we are now only up now
$27,000 we were up 160 Grand but
honestly I see this John went a lot
lower so let me show you guys so right
now daily time frame has closed as a
beautiful magnif magnificent mag
magnificent beautiful daily pin bar
dogee red whatever you want to call it
rejecting from this level of resistance
level of support and level of support I
think that now we can have a quick daily
Wick match that Wick and then headed to
the downside now that's going to suck
because it's going to come right into
our entry points where we are in the
market and we obviously don't want to
see that but I can definitely see us
filling that ginormous Wick I love these
huge Wicks because usually price always
fills it when you're trading with the
trend right now the 4our is accumulating
it is having a higher low lower high
lower low beautiful shif the structure
and 30 minute time frame is still
bearish this is still a lower high this
to the lower low right now we just
simply have to continue to be patient
and wait for this to just have a
reaction to the downside we are
accumulating right at this area and
we're clearly rejecting a multiple times
it's pretty much destined for us to
continue going to the downside gbpnzd on
the other hand we are now officially
making it to the area of Interest where
we would be interested in taking the
trade and we're having a reaction from
that point I'm not interesting in adding
a position on this at all just going to
leave it like this to see what happens
and the Euro JPY I had pretty much the
move that I anticipated daily time frame
beautiful daily bearish engulfing well
almost engulfing Candlestick I could
anticipate price to continue heading to
the downside for now our only focus is
UJ and to me we still have plenty plenty
of downside
potential so probably going
to take another trade tonight you know
what I'm saying kidding kind to just
stay here and focus on the markets and
then next week are we honestly this week
we should start hitting the gym
again when was the last time we hit the
gym well you hit the gym probably like 3
weeks ago I hit the gym like this
morning oh that's [__] up you didn't
invite me dude that's how you know I did
it here at the house push-ups how many
push-ups you think I can hit back to
back I bet I could hit more than you
back to back Maria
Maria we need you to jump off of this
right
now okay hold it again turn it hold it
ready are are you sure you get us both
in the frame yeah are you sure yes do I
look talk down 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25
26 27 28 29 30
and my posture was for real that was a
good try my breath all right guys Trad
up
day this is why I didn't want to
celebrate earlier or be anywhere near
excited because I expected for something
like this to happen we are currently
down about
$25,000 in the account when we were up
earlier about 150,000 at the height of
it
what you think I'm going to just [__]
and cry right now no dude this is part
of the set and forget I'm going to
continue sticking to my trading plan and
let this [__] ride I am almost more
confident about this position compared
to USD CAD of last week if you guys were
in that series last week you guys would
know let me just show you guys the USD
CAD now is having a pullback right up to
144,000 once again so if I were to look
at this on The Daily time frame you guys
can see that the daily has created that
long Wick and I mentioned that it was
going to reach the top of that wi now we
just happen to be surpassing that which
is not good not good now we can
uh well honestly we can get stopped out
on this [__] I can't I'm not even going
to lie but you know what I'm still very
confident that we will fill that Wick I
do love how the structure is looking
like on the 30 minutes I love how it's
still bearish this is still technically
the lower high and this is still
technically the lower low if anything
I'm going to be interested in adding new
positions very very soon if I obviously
get a reaction from here and engulfing
how we've done here and how we've done
here I'll probably add a position but
until then I'm going to continue to set
and for get GBP nzd the trade we did not
take is having very nice move it's
usually how it goes I do think that it's
going to continue going to the downside
and if we do manage to have a little
lower high I might consider entering
positions to the downside so for now
again we set up foret here Euro JPY I
think it can make it up a little bit
higher be this that structure in the EMA
to them s so if that has that little bit
more of a pushup to that cell then that
means that USD JPY probably has a little
bit more of a pushup to that
cell so for now just going to sit on our
hands and be patient and uh as of right
now now 10:38 at night we're down
24,000 it's not that
bad you look like
[__] I just got dided not actually dided
all right I don't want that to get the
wrong message across the markets Diddy
did the did out of me look at this price
went not only straight into our stop-
loss but a complete violation break
through the previous structure level
almost through the screen and out the
[__] roof we just got Diddy DD in the
DD is that even real [__] you
know I'm supposed to be raging right now
I would be throwing the chair I would be
throwing the astronaut I would go crazy
shoot the screen but you know what this
there's nothing to rage about I I can't
I would take this trade 10 times over
every single time it were to give me the
opportunity luckily we did not risk much
on the position we are only back at
135,000 and we only took about a
$68,000 loss on the account which given
this trade I should have risked 100% but
I explain to you the higher I go in the
account I lower my Risk by 20 5 to 50%
so I'm not even mad I I I'm not it's
just it's one of those losses with this
type of approach but look at this like
we got did didy so [__] crazy we have
a beautiful daily bearish engulfing
Candlestick 1 2 3 4 5 six days rejecting
from level of support support and
resistance daily bearish pin bar the
last thing I would [__] expect is
this didy what the [__] so when you go
to the 4our you see a beautiful 4our
lower low creating a lower high at the
area of Interest resistance round
psychological level 4our engulfing 1
hour left head right
shoulder it's everything you would want
to see in a position I can nearly almost
almost guarantee you that out of 10
positions that you were to take on this
you will have a minimum 40% win rate so
you'll lose six of these you get six
didies and then you'll get six
four who should the four what are the
what's like a w what's a represent
because didd equals L what's a
representation of a w 69 you
get that's so far from a w I know that's
another L you'll get four W's and then
six L's let's say you risk 1% it's minus
6 on these four that you win let's say
you get a minimum of a 1 to two risk to
reward which we were aiming here for a 1
to 3.8 realistically a 1 to four so
these four positions 4 * 4 what is it 16
so subtract the 6% that you just lost on
these you're left with 10% so this is a
pattern that I'll take every single time
can't even make something super
entertaining um not me being real like
there's other times where I'm generally
actually mad or pissed off but bro now I
I accept this loss fully because I will
take this trade every single time now on
the other hand let me just put this John
up we're going to probably have to break
our trading plan it's going to have to
happen and we might have to break our
trading plan because I don't see the
three markets that we were interested in
trading this week to give us a good
opportunity and I still want to hit the
goal for the week but I have to keep in
mind I know I made the same mistake
exactly one year ago I blew the
challenge on NFP what a coincidence that
this Friday is NFP the first Friday of
every month is NFP and literally one
year ago I blew the challenge on a
Friday with NFP when we were at the same
exact amount on the balance of the
challenge [__] gives me goosebumps I
don't know that's pure coincidence but
this is me showing you guys that I
learned from my lessons and that I am
not going to make the same mistake again
so this right now is not giving me a
solid opportunity I am no longer
executing a position in this market
especially after a move like that the
move is B basically gone next is going
to be gbpnzd so if we would have taken
this position we would have actually
taken a loss because price did not have
the whole entire move how I anticipated
even though I still like the fact that
we could still potentially have a
reaction from here to the downside and
then we have Euro JPY which we were
anticipating for price to have a
reaction from here to then head to the
downside but we did not have that move
how we wanted to obviously because of
the JPY what happened on USD JPY
happened on your JPY as well so none of
these three markets are super super high
probability trade setup except this one
I can still enter a good trade setup on
gbpnzd I can still get a price to come
up here into round Cy logical
2.12 then wait for the Shi to structure
to then sell so we could probably wait
for that but what I'm going to do now is
I'm going to look for different markets
that I was analyzing on Sunday swings
and I wasn't giving it the best grade to
trade for this week and see if I can
find an opportunity there that is
breaking my trading plan because I would
never go back into the markets that I
did not add to the watch list and add
them to my watch list because I don't
find Opportunities the current markets
that is me being greedy and going to
find these markets but I know what I'm
doing I accept it I know I'm breaking my
trading plan so what happens when I do I
have to drive the Beetle and I accept
that I know I'm doing something wrong
it's not like I'm not doing something
wrong and I'm not going to hold myself
accountable I know I'm doing something
wrong and I'm going to hold myself
accountable so I'm going to see if I can
find another Market if not we're just
going to focus on GBP nzd so until then
I don't
forget I found one I found one let me
take you off this actually I'm just
going to bring you with me like this all
right
boys we got the tripod in the house all
right boys so I actually found a very
decent opportunity in the market with
actually one of my favorite pairs which
is going to be GBP CHF so GBP CHF right
now on the daily time frame it is
clearly showing that it has a very
strong left head and then like a right
shoulder price is now pulling up to this
area of interest on the weekly time
frame you guys can see that we are
retesting this level of structure right
here the last week we had a weekly
bearish rection Candlestick and we are
cre kind of creating a doe right now
this week when you go down to the daily
daily you can see that the price action
is clearly not liking this area what I
don't love is that we are above this
level of support right here we're
clearly above it but I could see price
have a push to the downside and then I
when you go to the 4H hour you can very
very very clearly see that the 4 Hour
went from creating higher highs and
higher lows to now having a shift to the
downside side so if this were to be like
the middle of New York session or London
session I would take this trade pretty
much right now in a heartbeat but it is
currently 11: in the afternoon no I mean
it's 1:00 in the afternoon so there's no
more Market volume so I pretty much
can't take this trade anymore just
because we're at a session we can only
take a pre- London session which will be
like at 12:00 tonight midnight Miami
time and we have
gbpusd which ironically enough they're
both GBP pairs
but this one I'm actually interested in
buying it so we have a retest of this
structure level weekly time frame is
bullish daily time frame is bullish or
bearish depending how you want to look
at this but we are retesting this very
strong level of support and resistance
and is very well respected throughout
here and now we are above that zone so
we can see a push to the upside you can
see here on the 4our at the 4 Hour is
indeed having some type of a reaction
from that point but I think the only way
I can buy it is going to be at the break
and retest up here because I think price
could actually pull up into this area
and then have a reaction to then the
downside so I'm just going to be very
much on the lookout the 1 hour time
frame looks decent but if we break and
retest above this I'll be a lot more
interested in it so we have gbpusd now
for buys and GBP CHF for
sales or maybe even sales on gbpusd if
we pull up into here and then we have
nice rejection so for now all I can say
is stay tuned all right we F to the park
have to make sure that the B's a little
dirty
[__] okay this ball let's get the other
one can never get enough of these
balls no Diddy all right so today looks
like we're alone at the gym the rain
scared a little bit of people away but
we're not going to let that stop us look
at this we're the only people
here you know what that
means I don't really I don't really know
what that
[Music]
means oh [__] but trading is kind of
like playing basketball like right now
I'm playing basketball myself and it's
boring I have to catch M with rebounds I
have to hold myself accountable when I
miss I have to be here by myself and it
gets boring trading it's kind of like
that as well when you're trading by
yourself right now let's say you're in
your office you're in your living
room in your bedroom wherever you're
trading it gets boring so one of the
main reasons as well why I'm doing the
30-day boot camp is cuz I know when I
complete this 100 to the mill series I'm
going to be bored again so me taking on
this new challenge taking a hand
selected amount of people teaching them
how to trade taking them from Level 0 to
30 days live with me where I'm taking
you by the hand oneon-one it's fun it's
like playing basketball with a team with
some people that don't know how to play
you got to teach them how to shoot got
to teach them how to dribble sucks at
the beginning but the end result is fun
when you see that person that you didn't
know how to trade do something like this
I know I made it
no well you got to miss some too right
but the point is that I know that once I
complete the challenge I was going to be
bored so now that when I complete it I'm
going to take on this new challenge
which going to teach a hand select and
amount of people on how to trade using
my same exact set and forget strategy
the updated version on how I turn the
100 into the mill 30 days live with me
so more on that later because for right
now we can't do anything until we don't
complete the challenge because how am I
going to teach you how to do it if I
haven't even done it myself so for now I
and
forget today we're locking in for London
session part A th000 we've done this so
much already have you even showered
today I haven't I haven't I don't think
I've eaten today have I
eaten holy [__]
dude you see how skinny I am wow you
don't look fat holy
[__] yeah I haven't eaten today what
time is
it
11:06 at night who oh market update
hair's still looking like Frankenstein
or Albert Einstein I feel like Albert
Einstein right now like twitching out
and [__] genius bro you know Albert
Einstein has projects that sometimes
don't don't do well and right now we are
not doing well we're still at the same
exact spot still no new positions into
the account so our trade ideas are going
to potentially start moving as of right
now so we have gbpusd which we can now
see a double bottom from this area to
then buy daily time frame closed pretty
decent I like that little daily dogee at
this level 4our time frame Little D B
you know what I'm saying the 1 hour this
looks actually not that I this just
doesn't look like anything right so I
need to have some type of reaction and
then I'll enter this straight to the
upside but the real trade that I want to
enter is at the break and retest of this
and then next is going to be GBP CHF for
cells I love how this price action is
currently looking right now daily time
frame close with the daily dogee and if
you go down to the 1 Hour 1 hour has had
what looks to be like a little double
top I'm literally going to wait for a
break and retest under this area right
here so this is kind of like the
consolidation Zone it's in so I want to
have some type of break out of this and
then a quick retest to then sell a
little breakout then a quick retest then
sell everything depends on the price
action but I want to enter here but I
can't enter here right now I need the
breakout confirmation and then the pull
back to enter here I don't mind entering
a little bit lower but I just need the
confirmation that it's having a breakout
and time to move um and aside from that
GBP nzd is not giving us any entries
anytime soon so price completely blew
through the area of interest that we had
set up at
21200 and we can just wait for a little
quick break and retest to then sell on
the 4our if price were to decide to do
that not really interested in this and
then USD JPY just completely violated
our whole entire trade idea so our only
focus right now is GBP CHF for sales a
quick little day trade for a 1 to two
and G DP USD for little quick day trade
for
buys now Albert Einstein
out you're not going to say nothing
today huh you say nothing today huh
great update we are up
238,000 mother the [__] dollars you
know what I'm not going to rage again
I'm not going to get excited I'm like
I'm like I'm like ready I'm like ready
to [__] Dash and [__] you know
what one not only are we not near the
goal for the week the go for the week is
half a m so we're off by 1:30 and two
there's nothing to celebrate just yet
the trade has not closed do not get
excited Okay g GP CHF trade update so
right now we have three very unique
entries on GBP CHF and I want to explain
them to Perfection because this moved
very fast literally only like 4 hours
this is just one Candlestick so GBP CHF
we had the 4H hour bearish and golfing
how I wanted from that area and then we
obviously entered at the breakout of all
of this consolidation Zone here I
entered on this 1 in the morning
Candlestick as as it was getting ready
to close entered right there spread took
me a little bit down and then we add our
next entry on this 15-minute pullback so
we had the full move I'm like yes
amazing beautiful but then we had this
pullback and on this pullback I waited
for this engulfing confirmation we
entered on this pullback of this Wick
and then the next entry we entered at
the bottom of that rejection candle
right there and those are our three
entries we have our first one up here
our second one right here and our third
one right around here and our takeprofit
was very strategically placed at this
next 4H hour low so as you can see the 4
Hour is clearly bearish higher high
higher low D bearish lower low lower
high lower low lower high we're destined
to create a new lower low but up to
where up to this structure point and you
can clearly see that price has very well
reacted from that structure point this
is only a 1 to 2.7 risk reward and we've
risked a lot lot more than what we're
risking here on different markets this
move just happens to be very very
volatile like we're up 102 Pips right
now or takeprofit 130 so I never close
my trades with the takeprofit numbers I
always close my trades manually and I do
it automatically so technically we're up
a 1 to two right now which is what we
would usually want from a trade but I
just see so much more downside Potential
from this trade but I don't know if I
see it like today this is what this
daily Candlestick has done and I don't
know how much more motion this shit's
got like I don't I don't know if it
could just today like you guys have to
be realistic with yourselves like you
could be right about the trade and my
analysis indicates to me that this trade
can make it all the way up to here but
when will it make it up to there today
tomorrow the next day the day after even
have that much time you look at the
calendar what is tomorrow tomorrow is
the first Friday which is NFP so we
Technic we technically only have the
rest of New York session today because
it is currently 9 in the morning and
then we have London session tonight and
then New York session on Fridays are
pretty whack so you have to ask yourself
do you think this daily Candlestick has
enough motion to keep going to this
level here probably not like if you just
measure this daily Candlestick right
here what was the last time you had a
daily Candlestick move that much right
let's go find out not here that one this
one day engulfed these two days engulfed
every single one of these days engulfed
engulfed engulfed like since
basically this day right here August
88th we haven't had a Candlestick this
big now yes usually whenever we have a
Candlestick that big the next days it's
the continuation but if you see right
here it's 2 days two days of just slow
down and then continuation do we have
time for two days days do we no because
then it's the weekend like these are all
these high Lev things that you have to
take into consideration when you're
deciding if you want to continue to hold
or close a position so for right now I'm
just going to wait
for this Candlestick to close in about
57 seconds to determine what exactly I
want to do hopefully what it does is the
same thing as op is we decide to watch
it and then what happens if right that
would that' be pretty sick I not going
to lie all right GBP USD so we can
explain these we're waiting for a double
bottom to then buy no trade we did not
buy GBP and ZD had to move exactly how
we wanted to and it's having a very
clean bearish engulfing reaction from it
this is probably a trade that I'll be
interested in taking next week I think
tomorrow it's going to have a pullback
Friday nothing Monday nothing and
Tuesday it will have the push so we can
have that trade on Tuesday USD JPY just
completely continued to the upside and
then your JPY is kind of just
consolidating here so GBP
CHF is
currently um 3 2
1 well this is not epic all right do we
hold do we close do we hold do we close
um dude honestly I feel like I could
[__] feel that all day I would say
let's look at another 15 minutes like
let's wait for this 15-minute
Candlestick cuz D I definitely feel like
I could have a reaction from here here
cuz look like right where price is at if
you look left support resistance
resistance like it's a very well
respected level and I think it could
respect it man I really do think my goes
again half a m i don't know how much
I'll be when I'm down here like I don't
know if I'll be up to like
400 I'm not being greedy by the way just
take that into consideration I'm just
maybe I am I'm already driving the beo
today so what's the big deal all right
we'll wait I'll make a decision soon
update you guys all right boys I had to
stand up for this one trade update we
closed at
332,000 trade history as you guys can
see we have officially closed the
position at the highest point keyw we've
closed the position we were just up
400,000 we lost 70k just because of
[__] floating [__] clean
out well you know what we actually want
to trade we shouldn't be doing that
right sorry
we have Sensei here Sensei my friend my
friend so trade update Clos the
position right around here so I came to
the executive decision that you know
what we did have a rejection from this
level of support the strong thing the
smart thing to do is to not hold and be
greedy so we decided to just literally
close our position here out of 1 to two
I do see this having a downside
potential but not without a pullback and
I don't want to handle the pullback so I
think it's actually the fastest trade in
the whole entire challenge basically
took like 5 6 hours that being said it
is currently
9:27 and we're done for the day now
we're going to drive the Beetle and see
where the day takes us I think it's time
for me to be able to [__] fix up my
hair you know finally change clothes and
change clothes I haven't showered in 2
days I have showered I'm just wearing
you guys notice it's the same hoodie
different shorts
I bet you didn't notice that so we are
going to set and
forget got to make sure it's
neutral no
Diddy come
on come
on no
horn oh how can I forget bro forgot to
turn on the switches dude
[Music]
all right we cannot risk this turning
off so we got to go oh we got to move oh
we got to move no we don't have time we
don't have time we
have get out of the way get out of the
way oh my
neighbors right come let's go H want to
see
oh the
beetle I love this thing you Lo until
you [__] have to drive it everything
it's not that bad bro it's actually not
that bad it's not that bad right now but
bro when the sun is like this on you
with the heat it's terrible this bro has
no AC there's no [__] ventilation
nothing where the [__] the engine in
the back you have to drive with the pop
yeah cuz they probably to catch fire so
we have to like leave it like that
so that's it doesn't look bad right so
we're missing um the other one here but
you know doesn't have brake lights
doesn't have headlights nothing bro it
actually suits you bro you look like
that guy little car for a little guy and
yo that this this is the fuel tank right
here so if you crash no yeah lit [__]
car explodes in other words I mean bro
this is the engineers you weren't
surviving anyway you weren even if it
doesn't explode you wen't going to I
don't think it has airbags bro this is
from 66 dude
1966 probably like the fact this thing
still moves is actually cool pretty sick
yeah how did you even get where did you
find this Facebook Marketplace every
single night before I go to sleep I
dedicate 30 minutes to Facebook
Marketplace like I'll just put like the
geographic like national area I'll put
like Texas and you get some crazy ass
[__] bro I just
[__] oh
[Music]
oh I like your car thank you you want to
trade no why not thank you so
[Music]
much I didn't work she since she hit me
with
the I guarantee you I put up next to
this gold digger and my Bugatti and the
energy will be very very very
different y she got so close to the
other car she almost even hit it all
right so boys let this be a lesson for
you guys out there that it's not you
it's the circumstance that you're in and
all they care about is they want to feel
good about the circumstance that they're
going to potentially be a part of so I
get it I don't blame her but I obviously
know she's a gold digger I don't really
give a [__] I'm going to literally go
home now into my $3 million house and
she's probably going to have to go home
to her husband that's cheating on
her yo I love it she literally said
the successfully made it home once again
proves the method that this car does not
pick up
women morning ladies and gentlemen it is
currently 154 in the afternoon the
account is at the exact same as you guys
can see we have not entered any new
positions on the account which is kind
of interesting cuz this week we lost 100
no we lost 70,000 right off the bat and
then we made it back up by like almost
making a quarter which is good the goal
for the week was half Ma we're shy by
$170,000
which in retrospect is a lot monetarily
R but percentage wise of what we've done
to the account it's really nothing but
what we did do is avoid losses so GBP
CHF we were interested in taking the
loss here on Thursday night basically
Friday morning but we obviously weren't
interested in it and we were going to
enter the trade on this pullback once we
would have the rejection and the
engulfing on this pullback we never did
so we never entered this position simply
avoiding that loss and we close our
trade perfectly at this point right here
because I explained if we reach this
level we're then going to have a
reaction it's exactly what we did so we
avoided this loss right here and we made
sure that we close our our trade
perfectly because if we would continued
to hold and be greedy and want to catch
it all the way down here this trade
would have literally taken us out a
break even in a loss right now which
would suck let me take off these lines
then we have GP USD obviously never gave
us the entry we never took it GBP nzd we
never took this sell position as you can
see we were waiting for the pull back
into here wait for the entry signal to
then sell we got no entry signal no
shift to structure no rejection price
pulled up and it just never stopped and
we completely avoided this loss by
remaining patient and following this
trading plan USD JPY continue heading to
the upside and Euro JPY continue heading
to the upside so this week was pretty
decent we made a good amount of money
and uh all I can say is that next week
might be the week next week might be the
week where we actually turn the half
well not the half a mill into a mil cuz
if we turn 300K into a million that
means we would have to risk a 100% of
the account and catch a one to three
risk reward so we risk 100% catch a
quick intraday trade cuz to make a one
to three you're going to have to let it
ride for a little bit but if you're
risking that much not really I don't
know next week might be the week is what
I'm saying we can actually make the 300K
into a million if we catch a nice one 2
three risking
100% it's kind of interesting all right
so I might have just gotten the weirdest
thing in the mail right now but inside
of this letter was this not I don't even
want to touch it just look at it way is
I swear I'm not hacking you please watch
video and this was what was inside of
the
envelope I don't want to touch it cuz I
don't know if it's going to blow up so I
have it in here just in case if it blows
up it's a minor explosion not a major
explosion and I'm not going to open this
on my computer here I'm not [__]
[__] they actually might be hacking
me it might be a trick so we're going to
go to a public computer and plug it in
and see what this is this is mad weird
I've never gotten something this weird
in the mail Lally got here today I don't
know nothing in the
back let's go let's go to the computer
so we just got
here you hold it oh you're Savage bro
all right so we came to FIU FIU business
the school where they're going to teach
you how to be a successful entrepreneur
know no [__] here all right we just want
this random classroom classroom 154 all
right cool all right hand me the thing
where the hell did we put this
into I'm
nervous
FX I'm not a creep I swear I apologize
for the slight invasion of privacy and
s sight you [__] said USB to my
heart oh [__] you're not you're not
starting off good brother I've been
watching no wait Alex swing my first
name allit he sent another he said
another watch the other one FX Alex
G Mark Mark let me let me tell you
something right now Mark I I love the
creativity um I think it's very unique
but dude dude dude now I'm moving out
some more diversity on your channel man
some
diversity hey can't you want more
diversity than
this and this and this I'm I'm you got
Arab you got you got Dr
really I can't believe you said that
that's not true not aied team we are
qualified Personnel team I don't care if
you're black Asian fat Chinese woman
women I'm the only girl as well well you
do qualified welcome thank
you B also I quit hold on hold on hold
on hold on let me see what else one of
those movies the fact that he put
Kendrick and not Drake l oh that's it
that's it yeah Drake is way better than
Kendrick who the [__] is
Kendrick
Mark no but on the real Mark appreciate
the message um one you didn't leave a
caught action I don't even know how to
get in contact with you and two um yeah
that's all I can say but so yeah now
we're going to go to actually you know
what you know what actually me being in
this class right now makes me realize
something like imagine showing up to
this class every single day for 4 years
imagine sitting here listening to a
professor and writing down the
geographic algebra mathematician of
whatever the [__] to not even be really
successful in life like think about that
for a second people literally come into
here they sit around other unsuccessful
people and there is a 1% chance actually
under 1% chance according to this stat
from a very famous news article that
only 1% of people that go to college
actually become successful isn't that
sad that you come here for 4 years and
you know that maybe not even one of the
people sitting inside this class will
actually make it and have the life that
they really want I think that's sad
that's why in the 30-day boot camp that
I'm going to do do with 30 days just me
oneon-one you have not only more odds of
succeeding than an average person you're
going to have more odds are succeeding
than anybody in a classroom like this
and like literally in the 30day boot
camp that I'm going to do the success
rate of people having results 30 days 45
days after the boot camp is about a 50
to 60% so you being successful coming to
a corporate class like this is 1% the
odds of you being successful after 30
days is 50% isn't that crazy what
logically makes more sense spend four
years and tens of thousands of dollars
and be in an ugly environment like this
like I have to go take a shower I can't
believe I'm sitting in this chair
honestly I have to like that makes me
unprofitable or you can be part of a
winning circle that everybody has the
same ambition and the same drive to
actually be successful and you're
learning a craft that is going to make
you money coming into here and watching
a teacher that has no idea about money
has never had a business because if they
do they wouldn't be here teaching you
they would be running a business they
wouldn't be here making 40 50k a year
where you're literally just learning
from them what is being read off of a
tablet like this or being read off of a
book now your professor Alex G is here
take a seat sir take a seat sir did you
bring your
notes no did you do your homework no how
have you not done your [__] homework
now you get an F for not completing your
task now I failed you now you have to go
do it again is that the life you want so
what do you want to do you want to go to
school want be part of the 30-day boot
camp where do you think you're going to
make more money 30-day boot camp so why
you sitting in that [__] chair
that's what I'm talking about all right
guys so right now we're going to go pick
up my twin turbo I'm actually I'm
actually pulling up which is funny
you're actually pulling up yeah I'm down
the street perfect not it it so I told
these guys I'm like yo I want to wrap it
green for swing trading lab cuz we're
going to do the 30-day boot camp and all
that you know guys how I go crazy with
the marketing and stuff so and it's rear
wheel drive which is sick because I'm
able to do donuts so when I get it now I
get to Bugatti back on Monday I'm going
to do donuts around the Bugatti with the
green Lambo which is going to be sick
it's a wide body one in the whole world
so it's a pretty nice shade of green
what the why why is it
pink wanted a pink right no I said green
green yeah we only had pink though what
the [__] I'm
sorry kidding I got him I got oh [__]
actually honestly not that many people
could Rock pink cars I think one I'm one
of like this little bit amount of people
that could do it shout out to the number
one scammers in Miami uh charged me 8
Grand for this job which is [__]
crazy but you know what I'll pay it to
them all day because gets it done on
time you know bro I'll rip it here and
do donut you yeah that's what I was
calling you for okay sick yeah I do
[Music]
it now up Alex has he seen it or no yeah
he was here today oh you saw it what do
you think yeah it looks crazy bro you
really good I was telling Kevin it looks
like an Aventador looks really good a
few people have told me that really yeah
that's how you cheap your way into an
Aventador
[Music]
she